# Minho Park

Bundang-gu, Seongnam-si, Gyeonggi-do, Republic of Korea ☐ +821099689143 • ☑ m.park@kaist.ac.kr • ⑤ pmh9960.github.io

#### Research Interest

I have a strong interest in the domain of generating synthetic data via generative models. Currently, my research is centered on improving the vision-language models by utilizing large-scale pre-trained models in the data-scarce settings.

#### Keywords....

- Synthetic data generation via generative models
- Generative models, especially diffusion models
- Data-scarce settings

#### **Education**

Korea Advanced Institute of Science and Technology (KAIST)

Ph.D. in Artificial Intelligence, GPA: 4.00/4.3

Advisor: Jaegul Choo

Korea Advanced Institute of Science and Technology (KAIST)

M.S. in Artificial Intelligence, GPA: 4.00/4.3

O Advisor: Jaegul Choo

**Korea University** 

B.S. in Electrical Engineering, GPA: 4.11/4.5

Gyeonggi Science High School for the Gifted

Daejeon, Republic of Korea

Mar. 2024 - Present

Daejeon, Republic of Korea

Sep. 2021 - Feb. 2024

Seoul, Republic of Korea Mar. 2018 - Aug. 2021

Suwon, Republic of Korea

Mar. 2015 - Feb. 2018

### **Publications**

Under review

[U2]: Minho Park, Sunghyun Park, Jooyeol Yun, and Jaegul Choo. "Unlocking the Potential of Generated Datasets in Name-only Transfer of Vision-Language Models"

[U1]: Jeongho Kim, Gyojung Gu, Minho Park, Sunghyun Park, and Jaegul Choo "StableVITON: Learning Semantic Correspondence with Latent Diffusion Model for Virtual Try-On" [Paper] [Code] [Project Page]

Conference Paper.....

[C2]: Minho Park\*, Jooyeol Yun\*, Seunghwan Choi, and Jaegul Choo. "Learning to Generate Semantic Layouts for Higher Text-Image Correspondence in Text-to-Image Synthesis." *IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision (ICCV)*, 2023, Paris, France. [Paper] [Code] [Project Page]

[C1]: Jooyeol Yun\*, Sanghyeon Lee\*, Minho Park\*, and Jaegul Choo. "iColoriT: Towards Propagating Local Hint to the Right Region in Interactive Colorization by Leveraging Vision Transformer." *IEEE/CVF Winter Conference on Applications of Computer Vision (WACV), 2023, Waikoloa, Hawaii.* [Paper] [Code] [Project Page]

# Work Experience

**Qualcomm AI Research** 

Research Intern

O Data generation via generative models

Seoul, Republic of Korea

Mar. 2024 - Present

## **Academic Activities**

Conference reviewers: CVPR'24

Talks and Slides.....

- Various Types of Diffusion Models [Slides]
- Segment Anything [Slides]
- Classification with Foundation Models [Slides]
- Consistency Models and BOOT [Slides]
- DDPM [Slides]

## **Teaching Experience**

# Al Workshop Instructor.

**LG AI Research**: Data generation via generative models, *Feb. 2024*. **Deepnoid Tech Meet**: Various types of diffusion models, *Dec. 2023*.

SKT Market Top AI: Segment Anything, Sep. 2023.

YearDream School: Computer Vision, Aug. 2023 - Sep. 2023.

**AIGS Symposium**: Learning to Generate Semantic Layouts for Higher Text-Image Correspondence in Text-to-Image Synthesis, Oral session, *Aug. 2023.* 

**SKT Market Top AI**: Classification with foundation models, *Jul. 2023*.

Samsung-Elice Leader Digital Agility: Tutoring deep learning, Nov. 2022 - Nov. 2022.

Goorm K-Digital Training: Linear Algebra, Nov. 2022 - Nov. 2022.

## Teaching Assistant....

[Al618] Generative and Unsupervised Deep Learning: KAIST, Sep. 2023 - Dec. 2023.

DAVIAN basic study: Linear Algebra, Jul. 2023 - Aug. 2023.

SK ML Engineer Course: Computer Vision, Jun. 2023 - Jul 2023.

**DAVIAN basic study**: Computer Vision, Jan. 2023 - Feb. 2023.

DAVIAN basic study: Computer Vision, Jul. 2022 - Aug. 2022.

Samsung-SNU AI Expert Course: Linear Algebra, May. 2022

## Reference

Jaegul ChooKAISTAssociate Professorjchoo@kaist.ac.kr